$RNF_ModName	WattzIO - Radio Notifications
$RNF_Main_Intro	Disable radio station notifications to reduce HUD spam.
$RNF_Main_BulletA	- General (non-settlement) radio stations and Settlement Beacons have their own independent toggles.
$RNF_Main_BulletB	- Station Lost is hidden by default for both.
$RNF_Main_Credits	Mod by Abbie Doobie. Credit to Magicockerel (No Radio Station Notifications) for pointers on radio notifications.
$RNF_Page_General	General Settings
$RNF_Sec_Stations	Radio Stations
$RNF_Set_StationFound	Hide Station Found
$RNF_Set_StationFound_Help	Hides the notification when a radio station comes into range. Default: OFF.
$RNF_Set_StationLost	Hide Station Lost
$RNF_Set_StationLost_Help	Hides the notification when a radio station drops out of range. Default: ON.
$RNF_Sec_Stations_Note	Note that this includes Quest stations, such as distress beacons and signals.
$RNF_Sec_Beacons	Settlement Beacons
$RNF_Set_BeaconFound	Hide Settlement Beacon Found
$RNF_Set_BeaconFound_Help	Hides the notification when a settlement recruitment beacon comes into range. Default: OFF.
$RNF_Set_BeaconLost	Hide Settlement Beacon Lost
$RNF_Set_BeaconLost_Help	Hides the notification when a settlement recruitment beacon drops out of range. Default: ON.
